https://industrialladder.com/privacy-policy/

All Modular Racks
Prime Design "Professional Truck Rack"
*** Factory Upfit Allowances
Chevy Express - Regular Wheelbase (135")
All Chevy Express - Regular Wheelbase (135")
Chevy Express - Reg WB | Packages
Chevy Express - Reg WB | Partitions
Chevy Express - Reg WB | Ladder Racks
Chevy Express - Reg WB | Accessories
Chevy Express - Extended Wheelbase (155")
All Chevy Express - Extended Wheelbase (155")
Chevy Express - Ext WB | Packages
Chevy Express - Ext WB | Partitions
Chevy Express - Ext WB | Ladder Racks
Chevy Express - Ext WB | Accessories
GMC Savana - Regular Wheelbase (135")
All GMC Savana - Regular Wheelbase (135")
GMC Savana - Reg WB | Packages
GMC Savana - Reg WB | Partitions
GMC Savana - Reg WB | Ladder Racks
GMC Savana - Reg WB | Accessories
GMC Savana - Extended Wheelbase (155")
All GMC Savana - Extended Wheelbase (155")
All Stages & Planks
Aluminum Stages (Picks)
All Aluminum Stages (Picks)
"LEADING EDGE" Connectors
Self Retracting Lifeline (SRL)
Link Mfg. | Van Ramps
Prime Design "Professional Truck Rack"
Privacy Policy
When you visit www.industrialladder.com we hold your privacy concerns in the highest regard. This policy describes the personal information we collect about you, why we collect it, how we use it, and when we share it with third parties. Our policy also describes the choices you can make about how we collect and use your information. If our information practices change in the future, we will let you know by posting the revised policy on www.industrialladder.com.
What kind of information do we collect?
We collect information such as your name, e-mail address, billing address, shipping address, phone number that you provide to us when you place an order or request information. We also maintain a record of your order history. This information can be used to help us improve our site design and your online experience.
Extra secure credit card processing
We do not collect or have access to your credit card number. Your credit card information is handled by Authorize.Net, one of the leading internet credit card processing companies. They then interact with the banks directly. For information on Authorize.Net visit the following link http://authorize.net/company/aboutus/
How do we use your information?
When you place an order, we use the information you provide us to process and deliver your order. We will also send you an e-mail message informing you that your order has been received. Additionally, we may need to contact you via e-mail or phone if we have other questions or need information regarding your order.
Do we share your information with third parties?
We do not rent, sell, or share any personally identifiable information we collect to or with any unaffiliated third party without your consent.
How do you remove your information from our e-mail list?
We want to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. If you prefer to stop receiving information from us about our products via e-mail, please opt-out of receiving e-mails from us by clicking the “unsubscribe” on the bottom of the E-mail (Please allow 5-7 days to process your request). Please note that when you place an order, we will contact you via e-mail to confirm your order. In addition, we may need to contact you via e-mail or phone if we have other questions or need information regarding your order.
How and why do we use cookies on Industrialladder.com?
A cookie is a small data file that Web sites often store on your computer's hard drive when you visit. Industrial Ladder & Supply Co., Inc. uses cookies, but we do not store personally identifiable information in your cookie. The information stored in your cookie is only accessible by the Industrial Ladder & Supply Co., Inc. Web servers. Other Internet users and companies cannot access this information. We use cookies to improve your online experience. Cookies enable us to keep track of your order. They also allow us to recognize customers who have saved their information with us when they visit, and to provide those customers with their account information. If you save your info with Industrial Ladder & Supply Co., Inc. or order on our site, we use cookies to monitor and maintain information about how you use our site. You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your Web browser.
How do we make sure your order is secure?
Protecting your personal information is our priority. We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to ensure the security of your online information. To check the security of your connection, look at the lower left-hand corner of your browser window after you access our secure server. If you see an unbroken key or a closed lock (depending upon your browser), then SSL is active. To double-check for security, look at the URL line of your browser. If you have accessed a secure server, the first characters of our site's address should change from "http" to "https." To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect from you online.
What about links to other web sites and services?
www.industrialladder.com may contain links to other sites that are not under our control. These Web sites have their own policies regarding privacy, and you should review those policies before visiting these sites. Industrial Ladder & Supply Co., Inc. has no responsibility for linked Web sites and provides these links solely for the convenience and information of our visitors.
What if you have questions, comments or concerns?
If you have any questions, comments or concerns about our privacy policy please contact us via e-mail at customerservice@industrialladder.com
Thank you for reading our privacy policy.
Updated: October 6, 2019
OK
